statuswhatsapp.co.in 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Whatsapp Status & Shayari

Status Last Updated On:17/08/16

Thank you for visiting statuswhatsapp.co.in, a site designed to inform, inspire and entertain users all around the globe. This Privacy Policy is written to better explain how we collect and use your information.

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick Cookie  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, this site has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

Collection of Personal Information  
When visiting this site, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of https://www.statuswhatsapp.co.in then you may contact us.
